<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Church Media Lab</title>
    <link>https://churchmedialab.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Church Media Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://churchmedialab.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 004 - Camp &amp; Don&#39;t Be Afraid To Rent</title>
      <link>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/07/episode-004-camp-dont-be-afraid-to-rent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/07/episode-004-camp-dont-be-afraid-to-rent/</guid>
      <description>Show Notes After a long hiatus, WE ARE BACK! Camp season was busy and we talk about all of the adventures that we embarked on this summer. Join us as we talk about gear and approaches to production. We also talk about that sometimes renting is not a bad idea. Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to rent.
Show Links  Bird Dog PTZ Cameras Blackmagic Design ATEM Mini Live Production Switcher Blackmagic Design ATEM Mini Pro HDMI Live Stream Switcher Blackmagic Design ATEM Mini Extreme ISO Black Magic Design Cameras Borrow Lenses Camera Rentals Lens Rentals Camera Rentals MA Lighting Consoles &amp;amp; Software Waterproof USB Drive Case Neewer Lights Bagsmart Photography Backpacks Peak Design Camera Wrist Strap Cable Organizer Case Large Cable Organizer Case Apache Case (Amazon) Apache Cases (all sizes from Harbor Freight) Gerber Multi-Tool Gerber Muli-Tool Clip and Carry Sheath Anthony’s Media and Design Kits Brad’s A/V and Streaming Kits  Church Media Lab  Instagram Facebook  Anthony  Email Instagram Lnks  Bradley  Email Instagram Lnks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 003 - Gear You Just Can&#39;t Live Without</title>
      <link>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/04/episode-003-gear-you-just-cant-live-without/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/04/episode-003-gear-you-just-cant-live-without/</guid>
      <description>Show Notes Our third episode was all about gear. Not the big things, but the little things that make your life easier. Below you will find links to all of the products we talk about. Everything from budget video lights to audio cable testers, this episode has it all.
Show Links  Cable Tester XLR Sniffer Rechargeable Battery’s Anker USB3 SD Card Reader Anker USBC SD Card Reader USBC to USB3 Waterproof SD Card Case USB Drive Case Waterproof USB Drive Case Neewer Lights Bagsmart Photography Backpacks Peak Design Camera Wrist Strap Cable Organizer Case Large Cable Organizer Case Apache Case (Amazon) Apache Cases (all sizes from Harbor Freight) Gerber Multi-Tool Gerber Muli-Tool Clip and Carry Sheath Anthony’s Media and Design Kits Brad’s A/V and Streaming Kits  Church Media Lab  Instagram Facebook  Anthony  Email Instagram Lnks  Bradley  Email Instagram Lnks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 002 - All Things Livestream Part 1</title>
      <link>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/03/episode-002-all-things-livestream-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/03/episode-002-all-things-livestream-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Show Notes Our second show was all about live streaming. This episode was jampacked with a lot of information so if you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch it all the first time around we added a lot of links below. There was so much to cover that we only went over the basics. Our next episode will be the second part of live streaming where we cover advanced topics such as adding graphics and lyrics to your stream, advanced camera adjustments, lighting, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 001 - The Introduction</title>
      <link>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/03/episode-001-the-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://churchmedialab.com/posts/2021/03/episode-001-the-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Show Notes This is our very first episode of the Church Media Lab podcast. Meet the two host of our show, Bradley and Anthony. We have quite a few interesting shows planned so stay tuned. As of publishing this we are currently on Pocketcast, AnchorFM, and Spotify. Within the upcoming weeks our podcast should be available in more apps. If you have any media related questions or would like to submit a show topic, please drop us an email or leave a comment on our social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://churchmedialab.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://churchmedialab.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Church Media Lab Host Anthony Roberts Anthony currently server as Assistant Pastor at Abundant Life Church where he also oversees all things media and creative. Anthony also works as a freelance graphic designer. In addition to media and creative and you can usually catch him slapping the bass on Sunday mornings. With 15 plus years in the church media and creative world he hopes to bring insight, experience and encouragement to those working in church media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://churchmedialab.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://churchmedialab.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Anthony  Email Instagram Lnks  Bradley  Email Instagram Lnks  Church Media Lab  Instagram Facebook  Listen Here  Anchor FM Breaker Google Podcast Pocket Casts Radio Public Spotify Rss  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
